<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sky Reach</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bottom">Bottom</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open_navigation_drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close_navigation_drawer</string>
    <string name="Description">Om Sir is the owner of Sky Reach classes. According to him
    Students’ life is the best time when you can learn so many unknown and interesting facts.
        But this time is sensitive too as they need proper guidance and interest on their subject.
         So, for the right guidance, you should need to join the coaching classes.
        You can take tuition separately at your own home; no issue but coaching classes has some important role in the students’ life.

            Coaching classes are always played a role of proper guidance.
            If you want to stay in the competition then you need a regular and routine life without having any stress.
            Don’t force your children to attend the classes.
            Make them understand that this types of classes have  Actually attended a coaching class has lots of benefits which will teach you more and make you update more as this type of classes is full with fresh flocks of students and their ideas and curiosity.


            Coaching center is the place where you can get a good coach and Education is that powerful thing which makes you be a GOOD COACH.
            A good coach always tries to teach his/her students the best thing, so a coach always gives you the best and important information related to your studies.
            You will get compact and well-researched study materials from your center.
            If you do not get any points or if you face any problem regarding your studies then you can ask for the help of your coach.


    </string>
    <string name="AboutUs" formatted="true">
        \u2023 12 successful years in the field of education.\n\n
         \u2023 We have accomplished an astonishing growth to thousand of students over the years.\n\n
         \u2023 There are 4 branches of Sky Reach Classes.\n\n
         \u2023 We have a staff of more than 70 people including teaching and non-teaching members.\n\n
         \u2023 We conduct about 70 lectures per week at all our branches.\n\n
         \u2023 We have been producing H.S.C and S.S.C merit ranker\'s since 2008.\n\n
         \u2023 We conduct special lectures.
    </string>
    <string name="Vithalwadi">Vithalwadi\n
        5/7,Near Kamaladevi college,vithalwadi(E),Kalyan-421306.
    </string>
    <string name="Kalamboli">Kalamboli\n
    3rd Floor,F6-6,Sect,3EB/kalamboli(Post Office)-410218.
    </string>
    <string name="Titwala">Titwala\n
    1st Floor,Room 4 Dixit Building\nNear Shiva Shakha and Holy Rose School Manpada Road,Titwala(E).
    </string>
    <string name="Kalyan">Kalyan East\n
    Sahil Plaza,Near Gavdevi Road,Opposote Vighnharta Park,Hajimalang Road,Kalyan(E).
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
